tpww.net 2006-06-28

# TPWW.net - [ privacy policy ]

**[ privacy policy ]**  
This policy is to show the privacy throughout our site. Once you click on a link or move to another site you will be subjected to a new policy.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php).

 **Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Advertisements**

Our advertisements may contain cookies, which allow advertisers to track information about which sites you go to. For more information please visit our advertisers' official websites. 

**Personal Information**

TPWW currently does not require any personal information to be given out. Our staff will never ask anything personal.

**External Links**

We do have several links to other sites. We are not associated with these sites in any way, unless stated otherwise. 

**Public Forums**

We do have a forum which allows people to have discussions. All information is optional and posting is at your own risk. 

**Chat Rooms**

TPWW staff will never ask for personal information. Children under 13 years of age must have parent's permission. 

**[[tpww.net](http://www.tpww.net/) | [forums](http://www.tpwwforums.com/) | [headlines](http://www.tpww.net/headlines/) ]**
